Contact

Bjørndal, Granbergstubben 1275 Oslo, Norway +4741361459 (Mobile) sarathprakashofficial@gmail .com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarathprakash-649427251 (LinkedIn) sarathprakash.com/ (Personal)

Top Skills
Kubernetes
Docker Products
Azure Cosmos DB

Sarath Prakash

Full Stack .NET Developer Oslo, Oslo, Norway

Summary

I have been working in the IT industry for more than 8 years and have immense passion and enthusiasm for what I do. Successfully implemented more than 15 software projects, participating in full project life cycle. Scaling new heights of success and leaving a mark of excellence in assignments. A challenging career in Business Analysis and to be associated with a progressive organization which can provide me with a dynamic work sphere to extract my inherent skills as a Professional, use and develop my aptitude to further the organization's objectives and attain my career targets in the progress.

Skills:- ASP.NET, .NET Core 6, Web API, C#, SQL DB, Cosmos DB, Azure DevOps, Azure Functions, Dapper, Entity Framework Core, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML5, WCF, MVC, Automation Testing, Penetration Testing, xUnit, Selenium, Team City, Octopus, Scrum Agile Methodology.

Experience

Riverty Senior Software Engineer January 2023 - Present (7 months) Oslo, Norway

KPMG

Consultant
March 2020 - December 2022 (2 years 10 months)

UST System Analyst February 2019 - March 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Xerox Senior Software Development Engineer Page 1 of 2 June 2017 - February 2019 (1 year 9 months)

Orion Innovation Software Engineer August 2015 - April 2017 (1 year 9 months) India

Estrrado

Associate Software Engineer August 2012 - August 2015 (3 years 1 month) India

Education

Lourdes Matha College of Science and Technology, Kuttichal, Thiruvananthapuram Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (August 2007 - June 2011)